My revenge has just begun.
I know you like me.
In this family,
I've never been wary of you
Call my name
Yeo-gyeong.
Say it again.
Soft scenery.
I thought my leaving
would at least make him feel guilty.
If you betray me again,
and abandon me,
You're so beautiful.
How can I bear to do that?
Don't you like stimulation?
Ingrid.
You've gone too far.
Long Yue.
I was just joking with her.
Young Master.
Don't say that about Miss Leng.
You've suffered so much outside.
Shouldn't she be spoiled when she comes back?
My lady.
You're suddenly so nice to me.
Did you poison me?
No.
Spit it out.
What are you doing?
Are you okay?
Let me see.
Xiao Mei.
Aren't you
allergic to mango?
Why are you...
I was allergic to mango when I was young.
But later,
I'll be fine when I grow up.
I'll do it.
You're awake.
Take the medicine.
You're allergic to mango.
Why did you eat it?
Because I want to prove to you.
Prove what?
He Mei is fake.
I've checked
the paternity test.
He's really my biological son.
But I believe Young Master
must have doubted it.
If you believe me,
we can cooperate.
Then why are you
allergic to mango?
In this world,
many people are allergic to mango.
But
the one who should be allergic
is not allergic.
Don't worry about it.
Have a good rest.
Master.
Now that Xiao Mei is back,
the stone in your heart
should be landed.
Master,
At your 60th birthday banquet,
as long as Xiao Mei comes back,
the inheritance
the inheritance?
Don't ask
don't ask.
You're dying.
You can't take so much money with you.
Why are you still thinking about it?
I'll listen to you.
Be gentle.
I'm already here.
Handsome.
Are you sure?
He Mei worked here?
Okay.
I'll call you.
Want one?
No, thanks.
Then drink with me.
No.
I'm looking for someone.
Who are you looking for?
Her name is Lulu.
She used to work here.
Mom, are you looking for Lulu?
So you're here for Lulu.
She quit long ago.
But
we have a new batch of girls today.
They are all better than Lulu.
Good evening, sir.
It's her.
I knew it.
There's always one you like.
I work as a nanny during the day
and work at night.
What are you thinking?
I came here for the same purpose.
I found that Ho Mei
worked here.
But you can't...
I'm fine.
I found out that
she worked here when she was 18.
So she never went to America.
Go back first.
Leave everything to me.
I'm not going back.
Since Young Master
cooperate with me,
I'll investigate it myself.
It's not as simple as you think.
Just bring the real He Mei
to me,
I'll trust you.
Okay.
Beauty,
Let's have a drink.
We're already here.
Stop pretending to be innocent.
Brother.
It should be fine.
Why are you laughing?
It looks like an idol drama.
What else?
I can't watch you being bullied.
Unfortunately,
I couldn't find anything.
A rich young master like you
shouldn't be here.
I'm good at this.
Come with me.
You mean
He Mei's biological father?
To be precise,
Lulu's biological father.
She is not the real He Mei.
If you don't believe me,
they can do another paternity test.
I trust you.
Now,
can we work together now?
Help!
What's wrong?
Brother.
Someone put the picture of the dead on my bed.
It's okay.
Isn't that our mom?
Can't you recognize me?
I was just scared.
Do you
this person.
Are you crazy?
My dad...
Deyou.
Who is this?
I don't know him.
Are you still pretending now?
You set me up.
Your biological father
is now in the ICU.
but you treat other people as your father.
Do you think you've let him down?
I'm sorry.
I have my reasons.
Actor.
Performance form.
Jia Ning.
Mr. Hu.
Cao Zhen.
Mr. Kim.
Li Hui.
Su Bao Sheng.
Zhang Jian Wei.
[Zhang Jianwei]
Zhao Xi Xi.
Liu Mingyue.
Dong Jian Ning.
Dong Changwei.
Xia Zhenzhen.
Liang Jiang Kun.
Kang Guantao.
Rong A 52.
Cao Guangwei.
Shao Wenkang.
Nie Hao Jin.
Zhang Wen Fan.
Wang Cheng.
Wang Liang Guo.
Xiao Helong.
Guo Wenhua.
Zhang Yandong.
Gan Guo Qiang.
Gan Yu Jin.
Uncle Song.
Fan Nannan.
Chu Kunlun
Wang Congyi
Meng Hao Li.
Guo takes advantage.
Sheng Guang Hui.
Meng Yanyan.
Wu Lin Zhe.
Shi Shaohai.
Meng Xiangjun.
Li Yuling
Guo Wei.
Fan Quanbao.
Lai Zeping.
Liu Yishuang
Lulu Li.
Song Di
Guo Hongpeng.
Wang Xiaozhen
Yang Chen.
Lanhua Wang.
Wu Yunzhao
Wu Zhiqiang.
Bill.
Chen Yanlin.
Wang Jiying.
Meng.
Liu Jing Zhe.
Shi Tongrui.
Li Yuankang.
Ma Peng Cheng.
Zhao, Yang.
Zhang Chi.
Zhang Zhuang Zhuang.
Zhang, Fang.
Li Jiao.
Su Yanglin.
Jiang, first.
Zhao Chao.
Jin Ruliang.
Wang Jinzhe.
Zeng Zhenzhen.
Chen Gong Shuo.
Ren Meiyu.
Yao Can.
Hu Wenyue.
R.E Ailizati.
Zheng Jianjian.
Tian Ye.
Zuo Chunyang.